<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WOOSC - Wickwar Out Of School Club</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/</link><description>Recent content on WOOSC - Wickwar Out Of School Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://woosc.org.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arrivals and Departures</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/information/arrivals_and_departures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/information/arrivals_and_departures/</guid><description>Arrivals Before School Club: Children should be brought into the Community Room from 7.45am onwards and parents / carers must sign the children in stating their time of arrival. After School Club: Juniors will make their own way from their classroom to the club premises on site at AHPS. Reception and infant children will be met by a member of club staff directly from their classroom and escorted to the club premises.</description></item><item><title>Celebrations</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/celebrations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/celebrations/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Club absence</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/information/club_absence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/information/club_absence/</guid><description>Please note that the Club must be informed if your child/ren are booked into the After School Club but will not be attending, for example, going to a friend’s house. If we are not informed, your child will be classed as ‘missing’ and the Missing Child Policy procedures will be put into action, which could result in the police being informed.
If your child is unwell and therefore will not be attending a booked Before School session, please telephone the club by 7.</description></item><item><title>Craft</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/craft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/craft/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Galleries</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/home_page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/home_page/</guid><description>
PLay
Sports
Craft
Visits
Our Envrionment
Celebrations</description></item><item><title>General Information</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/about-us/</guid><description>Note that where references are made to ‘school,’ ‘school clubs,’ ‘class teachers,’ ‘playground’ and ‘perimeters of the school’ then this refers to the arrangement at Alexander Hosea Primary School (AHPS).
Wickwar Out of School Club (WOOSC) provides before and after school care for children from the age of 4 up to Year 8 of secondary school. WOOSC may offer to provide holiday care only for children from the age of 4 up to Year 8 of secondary school where numbers and staffing allow information available on request.</description></item><item><title>Menu</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/food/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/food/</guid><description>This is an example of the food we offer to the children each week.
Day Afternoon Food Monday Hot-dogs Tuesday Filled Rolls Wednesday Pancakes/scones/crumpets Thursday Wraps Friday Crackers with cheese or ham/beams on toast/brioche We offer fresh fruit and vegetables every weekday, as well as Toast, croissants cereal with milk or juice and a selection of spreads every weekday morning.
We do cater for allergies as long as we are aware of them</description></item><item><title>Newsletters</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/newsletters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/newsletters/</guid><description>To see our latest newsletter, click the link below.
2022-08 Term 1 Newsletter.pdf
2024-01 Term 3.pdf 2024-02 Term 4.pdf 2024-04 Term 5.pdf 2024-06 Term 6.pdf</description></item><item><title>Opening times and charges</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/information/opening_times/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/information/opening_times/</guid><description>Please be aware that in extreme weather conditions where travelling could be hazardous or Alexander Hosea Primary School is closed, Wickwar Out of School Club will not open.
Session Type Times Cost Before School Session 7:45 AM - Start of School Regular £6.50 Casual £7.00 After School Session End of School - 6:00 PM Regular £12.50 Casual £13.00 Holiday Club
8:00 AM - 6:00 PM £35.00
8:00 AM - 3:00 PM £27.</description></item><item><title>Our Development</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/development/</guid><description>For many years we have been trying to improve the outside environment as the inside areas we have can get noisy.
As of covid, we are trying to encourage outside playing more as it is healthier for the children and gives them more freedom on what to do
To help with this, we have been given funding for:
Outside lights so the children can play outside during winter and autumn months while still being in the light.</description></item><item><title>Our Environment</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/our_environment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/our_environment/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Play</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/play/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/play/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Policies</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/policies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/policies/</guid><description>Once registered with the club, you will be deemed to accept all the Policies and Procedures and Rules of the Club.
Please click on any of the policies listed below to view and/or download - hard signed copies are also available to be looked at, on request, within the club setting. Please note that policies are reviewed every academic year.
Absence and Sickness.docx
Administering medication.docx
Admissions and Fees.docx
Aggressive behaviour.docx
Anti-bullying.</description></item><item><title>Sickness, Accidents, First Aid and Emergencies</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/information/sickness_accidents_emergencies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/information/sickness_accidents_emergencies/</guid><description>If a child becomes ill at a club session, every attempt will be made to contact one of the people listed on the registration form to arrange collection of the sick child. The child will be cared for until collected. In the case of a minor accident, basic first aid will be administered. In the case of an accident, requiring more than basic first aid every attempt will be made to contact the parent/carer to advise or discuss with him/her the course of action to be taken.</description></item><item><title>Sports</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/sports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/sports/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Testimonies</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/testimonies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/testimonies/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Overall myself and my wife are very impressed by WOOSC and feel completely at ease with them looking after our daughter, and hopefully both our daughters from September&amp;hellip; The cost of WOOSC is good value and is a huge asset to the adjacent school to have such good childcare available practically on the same site.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I just wanted to highlight how happy my daughter has been at WOOSC, and there&amp;rsquo;s really nothing negative I can say about the care she receives&amp;hellip; The staff have always kept me updated and tried to help with any little issues the children may have around navigating relationships etc.</description></item><item><title>The Site</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/site/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/site/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Team</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/information/the_team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/information/the_team/</guid><description> Mary Simmons Business Manager I joined the WOOSC team as Business Manager in 2020 and enjoy working within a close-knit team of people.
Hilary Turner Day Manager With 25 years of experience in education and SEND, I believe play should be assessable to all children in order for them to learn and grow and develop healthy bodies.
Connie Harris Play worker Pat Trull Play worker Lynne Werreitt Playworker Sophia Turner Play worker Tracey Pearce Playworker Cerys Forsdike Playworker Teilo Coates Playworker</description></item><item><title>Visits</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/visits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/gallery/visits/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Whats On</title><link>https://woosc.org.uk/about/whats-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://woosc.org.uk/about/whats-on/</guid><description>What a brilliant holiday club we just had, come back later to see what else is on!</description></item></channel></rss>