<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Information on WOOSC - Wickwar Out Of School Club</title><link>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/</link><description>Recent content in Information on WOOSC - Wickwar Out Of School Club</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arrivals and Departures</title><link>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/arrivals_and_departures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/arrivals_and_departures/</guid><description>Arrivals Before School Club: Children should be brought into the Community Room from 7.45am onwards and parents / carers must sign the children in stating their time of arrival. After School Club: Juniors will make their own way from their classroom to the club premises on site at AHPS. Reception and infant children will be met by a member of club staff directly from their classroom and escorted to the club premises.</description></item><item><title>Club absence</title><link>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/club_absence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/club_absence/</guid><description>Please note that the Club must be informed if your child/ren are booked into the After School Club but will not be attending, for example, going to a friend’s house. If we are not informed, your child will be classed as ‘missing’ and the Missing Child Policy procedures will be put into action, which could result in the police being informed.
If your child is unwell and therefore will not be attending a booked Before School session, please telephone the club by 7.</description></item><item><title>Opening times and charges</title><link>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/opening_times/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/opening_times/</guid><description>Please be aware that in extreme weather conditions where travelling could be hazardous or Alexander Hosea Primary School is closed, Wickwar Out of School Club will not open.
As of: xx/xx/xxx (to be reviewed)
Session Type Times Cost Before School Session 7:40 AM - Start of School Regular £4.50 Casual £4.85 After School Session End of School - 6:00 PM Regular £9.00 Casual £9.50 Holiday Club - Half Day - AM 8:00 AM - 12:30 PM £15.</description></item><item><title>Sickness, Accidents, First Aid and Emergencies</title><link>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/sickness_accidents_emergencies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://t-m-coates.github.io/woosc-website/information/sickness_accidents_emergencies/</guid><description>If a child becomes ill at a club session, every attempt will be made to contact one of the people listed on the registration form to arrange collection of the sick child. The child will be cared for until collected. In the case of a minor accident, basic first aid will be administered. In the case of an accident, requiring more than basic first aid every attempt will be made to contact the parent/carer to advise or discuss with him/her the course of action to be taken.</description></item></channel></rss>